©
© P @ rM ! NdeR
© P @ rM ! NdeR M @ nkÖÖ
© P @ rM ! NdeR M @ nkÖÖ ™
© P @ rM ! NdeR M @ nkÖÖ ™ Mobile - + 919815899536
WOMAN : Alex .
Tod and George 's dad just called .
He 's picking you up at 3 : 30 tomorrow .
And the bus leaves the high school for the airport around 5 .
How 's my suitcase working out for you ?
Whoa , Mom , Mom , Mom , you gotta leave that on .
Yeah , it 's like the tag made the last flight without the plane crashing or anything .
So I figure it 's gotta be on the bag , or at least , with the bag .
For luck .
Where would you get a nutball idea like that ?
I 'm still here .
[ CHUCKLES ]
So 17 , on the loose .
Senior trip with your friends in Paris .
Ten days in the springtime .
Live it up , Alex .
You got your whole life ahead of you .
WOMAN : Alex .
Alex .
WOMAN 1 [ ON RECORDING ] : The white zone
is for immediate loading and unloading of passengers only .
No parking .
WOMAN 2 : Yeah , I 've been sitting here for over an hour .
Where are you ?
- Hey , Hitchcock . MAN : What ?
Let me give you a hand with this , man . There you go .
Carter , you dick .
- Schmuck . - Good one .
- You left this on the bus . - Oh , thanks .
Come on , let 's get your stuff together .
Hey , Christa . Hi , Blake .
What are you doing ?
He 's the man . The man .
All right , you guys got everything ?
Yeah , yeah . Dad , we 're all set .
[ SPEAKING IN FRENCH ]
Does that mean go ?
Don 't know .
Look , this is for both of you , all right ?
Have a great time .
- Thanks , Dad . - Yeah .
- Both of us . MAN : Let 's go .
JERRY : Alex . - Yes ?
- You take care of them . - I will .
You know , I didn 't think anything could look worse than my yearbook photo .
How do you think I feel having to look at you all the time ?
[ WOMAN SPEAKING IN FRENCH OVER SPEAKERS ]
[ SPEAKING IN FRENCH ]
- What the fuck does he want ? - Shh .
" The airport does not endorse solicitors . "
[ MURNAU SPEAKS IN FRENCH ]
Death is not the end .
It will be for you if you harass my students .
- Hare Rama . - [ MOUTHS ] Fuck off .
I have to ask you a few questions this evening .
Did you pack your bags yourself ?
Have your belongings remained in your possession the entire time ?
Mr. Browning ?
Oh , yeah .
Have you received any packages from persons unknown to you ?
- Same as your birthday . - What ?
September 25 , 9 : 25 .
Your birthday 's the same as your departure time .
MAN 1 : Because I looked at him .
MAN 2 : Are you sure ?
WOMAN 1 : Lisa , wait up .
No , it 's okay .
Fuck , that was good .
Dick .
- Hey . TOD : Hey , George , Dad said both .
Both of us , all right , man ?
Just give me some cash .
Hey , hey , knock it off .
WOMAN 2 : Excuse me . MAN 3 : Catch .
You asshole .
- Thanks . ALEX : You 're welcome .
Alex , let 's go take a shit .
Why don 't you go by yourself ?
No , dude . Listen , okay ?
Listen , take some knowledge .
We 're about to board a seven-hour flight .
The toilets in coach are barely ventilated closets , all right , if that .
Now , let 's say halfway through the flight , your body wants that food out .
You gotta go torque a wicked cable .
And then right after you , like , directly after you walks in Christa or Blake .
You want them to associate you with that watery sting in their eye ?
That reflexive gag at the back of their throat ?
[ JOHN DENVER 'S " ROCKY MOUNTAIN HIGH " PLAYS OVER SPEAKERS ]
John Denver .
Died in a plane crash .
WOMAN [ OVER SPEAKERS ] : Ladies and gentlemen , thank you for your patience .
At this time , we would like to begin preboarding
of Volée Air Flight 180 to Paris through Gate 46 .
[ JOHN DENVER 'S " ROCKY MOUNTAIN HIGH " RESUMES PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS ]
Anyone seen Billy Hitchcock ?
How did we lose him ?
[ SPEAKING IN FRENCH ]
Go . Go .
Go . Ow .
Ow . That hurt .
[ BABY CRYING ]
WOMAN : Oh , my little baby .
That 's a good sign .
The younger , the better .
It 'd be a fucked-up God to take down this plane .
Hi .
A really fucked-up God .
Yeah .
TOD : Hi . - Hey , Tod .
Hello . How you doing ?
I 'm gonna sit here .
[ AIR HISSING ]
- Can you switch seats with Christa ? - Oh , God .
You know , I would , but I got a bladder thing .
It 's a urinary tract infection .
Let 's go ask Alex .
Alex , could you trade seats with Blake so she and I could sit together ?
She asked Tod , but he said he had some sort of medical thing .
Please ?
Yeah .
You 're so sweet .
Thanks , Alex .
Thank you , Alex .
You 're welcome , you 're welcome , you 're welcome .
[ MOUTHS ] Fag .
Did you really think we 're gonna titty fuck them over Greenland ?
You know , because of you , I gotta sit here and watch fucking Stuart Little .
Thank you .
Thanks , man .
That 's great .
Sorry I 'm late .
That 's my seat right there .
TERRY : Hello ?
- I 'm going that way .
WOMAN 1 [ OVER SPEAKERS ] : May I have your attention ?
To properly fasten your seat belts , slide the flat portion into the buckle .
- -equipped with six emergency exits : two in front , two over the wing , two in the rear .
All exits are clearly marked .
Follow the red exit signs and public lighting in the aisle way .
MAN [ OVER SPEAKERS ] : Flight attendants , prepare for departure .
[ SPEAKS IN FRENCH ]
WOMAN 2 : All right .
- All right , all right .
Yeah .
Whatever .
Huh ?
[ MOUTHS ] It 's okay .
- I wanna go . - It 's fine .
[ BOTH CHUCKLE ]
It 's okay , honey , I ... .
CARTER : What the ... ?
[ BILLY YELLS ]
[ YELLING ]
MAN : Oh , my God !
MURNAU : Everybody ... .
[ MURNAU SPEAKING IN FRENCH ]
No ! No !
Christa ! No !
Alex , could you trade seats with Blake so she and I could sit together ?
She asked Tod , but he said he had some medical thing .
Please ?
[ PANTING ]
TOD : What 's up , dude ?
Is there a problem , sir ?
What 's your problem ?
Alex , qu 'est-ce que c 'est ?
The fucking plane 's gonna explode .
Shut up , Browning .
You 're so not funny .
If this is your joke- -
It 's not a joke . It 's not a joke .
Alex , take it easy .
That 's it , sit down , Browning .
It 's going down .
We will remove you .
- I 'll remove him .
ALEX : I 'll remove myself .
- Excuse me . TERRY : Get off him .
- That 's my seat right there .
ALEX : This plane is going down .
FLIGHT ATTENDANT : Everybody in the aisle , off the plane .
ALEX : Get off the plane .
- Stay where you are .
- Just sit tight .
ALEX : The fucking plane is going down .
Go check him out .
See how he 's doing .
Okay .
- I got my ticket here . - Get off me .
Jerk .
- Hey . - You got this ?
No one gets back onboard .
- That 's my call . - Wait , please .
I 've got 40 students going to Paris . Please , please ?
Look , you must understand my position .
I understand , and I apologize for Alex .
But one of us needs to be on that plane .
I cannot let students go to Paris for ten days ... .
Carter , no .
- Sit the fuck down , Carter . MAN : Sit down .
TOD : Sit .
CO-PILOT : One of you can go on the flight . That 's it .
Larry .
Airline 's not taking this well .
They 'll let one of us back on .
The rest can take an 11 : 10 flight .
It gets in three- -
I 'll stay .
No , no , you know the whole French thing .
Get on the plane , it 's fine .
Hi , Mr. Murnau .
See , I was in the bathroom .
And the lock , it was stuck , and ... .
Oh , wait , I didn 't fight with anyone .
Damn .
Thanks .
I just- - I called your parents .
They 're on their way .
We should be going .
Alex , talk to me . Tell me what happened .
I saw it .
Like , I don 't know . I saw it .
I saw it on the runway .
I saw it take off .
I saw out my window .
- I saw the ground , and ... . - Carter .
The cabin , it starts to shake , right ?
And the left side blows up .
And then the whole plane just explodes .
And it was so real .
Just like how everything happens , you know ?
You been on planes that blew up ?
You must have fallen asleep .
Whoa , we get thrown off the plane .
We blow , what , a half a day in Paris
all because Browning has a bad fucking dream ?
But wait , " The plane , it 's gonna blow up , it 's gonna blow up . "
- Hey , hey , fuck you , Horton . - Tod .
The only trip you 're taking is to the fucking hospital .
TERRY : Get off him . LEWTON : Hey , hey .
TERRY : Alex , stop it .
MAN 1 : Come on , now .
There they go , here we stay .
You 're paying for my trip .
I wish you were on that plane .
- You fucking prick . BILLY : Oh , shit !
[ PEOPLE SCREAM ]
MAN 2 : Call it in . WOMAN : Security ... .
You 're looking at me as if I caused this .
I didn 't cause this .
Are there any survivors ?
How should I know ?
- What , you think I 'm some sort of- - ?
CLEAR : He 's not a witch .
Hello , I 'm Howard Seigel , National Transportation Safety Board .
We 've contacted all your families .
They are on the way .
Is there anyone here who feels they might need a little medical attention
or spiritual counseling at this time ?
LEWTON : What 's going on ?
Are there any survivors ?
Well , the cause for the explosion is still undetermined .
The Nassau County authorities are on the scene .
Naval Search and Rescue en route . We- -
[ WEINE CLEARS THROAT ]
Excuse me .
I 'm Agent Weine . This is Agent Schreck .
We 're with the FBI .
I understand how you all must be feeling right now .
I know it 's gonna be difficult .
We 're gonna ask you questions regarding today 's events
while they 're still fresh in your mind .
This will prove invaluable to our rescue attempts and any criminal investigation .
You said , " Listen to me .
This plane will explode on takeoff . "
How did you know that ?
I got this feeling .
This weird feeling .
Did you take any sedatives before boarding the plane ?
Did you take any sleeping pills , any narcotics , hallucinogens ?
- Alex , do you take any drugs ? - No .
I saw it .
I saw it happen .
I saw the plane explode .
Did the feelings have anything to do with your saying
that you wished that Carter Horton was on the plane just before it exploded ?
- No . - Then why 'd you say it ?
Because I really didn 't think it was gonna happen .
If that 's the case , Alex , then why did you really get off the plane ?
My brother , George , he told me to go and keep an eye on Alex .
And so he stayed , and ... .
He told me to get off the plane .
Larry Murnau said I should get back on , but I told him that he should go .
I sent him back on the plane .
All right .
Nobody forced you off the plane .
You said you weren 't friends with those that were .
So , Clear , why did you get off the plane ?
Because I saw and I heard Alex .
And I believed him .
[ SOBBING ]
Honey .
Oh , God .
There he is .
Over here .
Thank you for the ride .
WOMAN [ ON TV ] : You 're looking at the first piece of debris
to wash ashore from Volée Air Flight 180
which erupted shortly after a 9 : 25 p.m. takeoff
from John F. Kennedy Airport in New York .
There are no known survivors .
However , Coast Guard and Naval Search and Rescue efforts
are continuing at this moment even as jet fuel burns on the ocean 's surface .
Authorities are pessimistic about the possibility
of finding anyone alive from the ill-fated flight .
All 287 passengers are feared dead .
Amongst the travelers , a class of 40 students and four teachers
from Mount Abraham High School in southeast New York
en route to Paris on a field trip .
There are reports that several students were removed from the aircraft
moments before departure .
However , investigators remain guarded about the specifics of this incident .
Authorities from the National Transportation and Safety Board
and the Federal Bureau of Investigation have arrived at JFK
to begin the initial investigation .
Eyewitnesses at the airport , as well as on Long Island
report seeing the plane explode .
No other aircraft were visibly near Flight 180 .
At JFK , air traffic controllers are corroborating
these eyewitness accounts .
After the explosion , debris apparently rained into the Atlantic Ocean for several miles .
However , investigators are cautious about verifying these accounts
believing they 'll learn more from the found debris when daylight arrives .
MAN : Thirty-nine days have passed
since we lost our 39 loved ones , friends and teachers .
As each day passes without a determining cause for the accident
we ask ourselves , " Why ? "
Ecclesiastes tells us :
" Man no more knows his own time than fish taken in the fatal net
or birds trapped in the snare .
Like these , the children of men caught when the time falls suddenly upon them . "
And so , before we can heal
before we can escape the presence of death and time
we must mourn and celebrate theirs with this memorial .
[ PLAYING GUITAR ]
[ MAN SINGING ]
I hope you don 't think because my name ain 't up on this wall
that I owe you anything .
I don 't .
Because all I owe are these people .
To live my life to the fullest .
Why don 't you stay off the J.D. , then , huh , Carter ?
Listen . Don 't you ever fucking tell me what to do , all right ?
I control my life , not you .
Carter .
I 'm never gonna die .
Hey , Alex .
- Hey . - Hey .
I took my driver 's test last week at the DMV .
Got a 70 . It 's the lowest score you can get , but I passed .
When I was done with the test ... .
You know the guy that drives with you ?
- Right . - Yeah , well , anyways .
He goes , " Young man , you 're gonna die at a very young age . "
Yeah . Yeah .
Is that true ?
Not now , not here , not ever , Billy .
If I ask out Cynthia Paster , will she say no ?
Fuck .
- Okay . - Yeah .
Yeah .
- Miss Lewton- - - Don 't talk to me .
You scare the hell out of me .
TOD : I 'm gonna go up .
© P @ rM ! NdeR M @ nkÖÖ ™
Hey .
I don 't want you to take this the wrong way .
But I miss you , you know ?
Yeah .
Yeah , I miss you too .
But my father , you know , he doesn 't understand .
Yeah .
Hey , look , when he gets over this thing
you and me , little road trip to the city , you know ?
Catch the Yanks .
Yeah . Yeah , all right , we 'll do that .
Cool .
- Look , I 'd better go . - Yeah .
This thing Miss Lewton showed me in class , they 're gonna let me read it .
It says what I 'm feeling .
Take care , man .
©
© P @ rM ! NdeR
© P @ rM ! NdeR M @ nkÖÖ
Because of you , I 'm still alive .
Thank you .
TOD : " We say that the hour of death cannot be forecast .
But when we say this , we imagine that the hour is placed
in an obscure and distant future .
It never occurs to us that it has any connection
with the day already begun .
Or that death could arrive this same afternoon .
This afternoon , which is so certain
and which has every hour filled in advance . "
[ JOHN DENVER 'S " ROCKY MOUNTAIN HIGH " PLAYS ON STEREO ]
[ MUSIC STOPS ]
[ OWL SQUEAKS ]
[ GRUNTING ]
[ MAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY ON RADIO ]
[ SNORING ]
What happened ?
Where 's Tod ?
CLEAR : Alex .
Get out of here .
- Didn 't you see it ? - What happened ?
You caused Tod so much guilt over George staying on the plane , he took his own life .
- No . MAN : Time to go .
Look , he wouldn 't do that .
Okay ? He said to me we 'd be friends again after you got better .
Why would he make plans with me if he was thinking about killing himself ?
Mr. Waggner .
- Mr . Waggner . MAN 1 : Here we go .
Easy .
All right .
Here we go .
MAN 2 : Let 's go .
[ BLOWTORCH IGNITES ]
CLEAR : Almost autumn .
It 's only the end of June .
CLEAR : Yeah , but everything 's always in transition .
If you focus , one week into summer
you can feel almost feel autumn coming .
Kind of like being able to see the future .
Why were you at Tod 's house last night ?
I 've seen enough TV to know that the FBI doesn 't investigate teen suicides .
They were there last night .
They don 't have a clue
what caused the crash .
They haven 't ruled out anything .
The fact that seven people got off the plane is probably weird enough .
Not to mention that one of those people had a vision , or whatever
of the plane exploding minutes before it did explode , is highly suspicious .
And it doesn 't help that the visionary 's friend just committed suicide .
Why were you there last night ?
Do you know what this is ?
This is a ... .
Who 's the spring-head guy ?
It 's you .
Not a likeness .
It 's how you make me feel , Alex .
I 'm sorry .
You know , like you , the sculpture doesn 't even know what , or why , it is .
It 's reluctant to take form .
And yet , creating an absolute but incomprehensible attraction .
In four years of high school , we haven 't said one word to each other .
At that moment on the plane , I felt what you felt .
I didn 't know where those emotions were from
until you started freaking out .
I didn 't see what you saw , but I felt it .
You can still feel it , can 't you ?
Something from that day is still with you .
I know because I can still feel you .
That 's why I was there last night .
You know , I 've never dealt with death before .
This could all be in our head .
It just feels like it 's all around us .
It ?
What if Tod was just the first ?
Of us ?
Is that something that you 're feeling ?
I don 't know , you know .
I just wish I could see him again .
One last time .
So maybe I would know .
Then let 's go see him .
[ GRUNTS ]
CLEAR : Easy .
Gives me a rush .
This place ?
Doing something I 'm not supposed to .
Come on .
Hurry up .
- Is that him ? - I think .
Why did they make him up like Michael Jackson ?
Yeah , that 's him .
But whatever it was that made him Tod is definitely gone .
Christ .
Shh .
Please .
You 'll wake the dead .
Why did his hand do that ?
Chemicals in the vascular flush create cadaveric spasms .
Look , um ... .
- I 'm his friend and- - - I know who you are .
What are all those tiny marks ?
Cuticle lacerations from pulling at the wire .
Pulling at the wire ?
If he was pulling at the wire , he wasn 't trying to kill himself .
It was an accident .
In death , there are no accidents .
No coincidences .
No mishaps .
And no escapes .
What you have to realize is that we 're all just a mouse that a cat has by the tail .
Every single move we make , from the mundane to the monumental
the red light that we stop at or run
the people we have sex with , or won 't with us
the airplanes that we ride , or walk out of
it 's all part of death 's sadistic design leading to the grave .
Design ?
Does that mean if you figure out the design , you could cheat death ?
Alex .
You 've already done that by walking off the plane .
Your friend 's departure shows
that death has a new design for all of you .
Now , you have to figure out how and when it 's coming back at you .
Play your hunch , Alex .
If you think you can get away with it .
But remember the risk of cheating the plan
of disrespecting the design could incite a fury
that could terrorize even the Grim Reaper .
And you don 't even wanna fuck with that Mack Daddy .
Okay , then , well ... .
Yeah , I 'm sorry we broke in and ... .
No harm . No foul .
I 'll see you soon .
ALEX : The mortician said that death has a design .
Okay .
I 'm talking about omens .
How do we know that just by sitting here , by sipping this coffee
or breathing the air or crossing the intersection
that we haven 't started in motion the events that will lead to our death
40 years from now , 10 years from now , tomorrow ?
We don 't unless we open ourselves up
to the signs it 's willing to show us .
I don 't understand .
Did you see Tod die ?
Did it happen again , like on the plane ?
No , no , it didn 't , but I mean , it might as well have .
This is a message of something , Clear .
Or someone , hinting at a design .
Total bullshit .
I mean , you can find death omens anywhere you want to .
Coffee . Starts with a C and ends with an E.
So does the word choke .
So , what , we 're gonna choke to death ?
I wanna hear you .
We 'll go nuts if you start with this shit .
The mortician said that death has a design , right ?
Now , what if you , me , Tod , Carter , Terry , Billy , Miss Lewton
messed up that design for whatever reason ?
I saw death 's plan , then we cheated it .
But what if it was our time ?
What if we were not meant to get off that plane ?
What if it still is our time ?
If it is , then it 's not finished .
And we will die now , not later .
Unless ... .
Unless we find the patterns and cheat it again .
[ NINE INCH NAIL 'S " INTO THE VOID " PLAYS ON CAR STEREO ]
After hearing you , I do believe
that Tod killed himself .
[ TIRES SCREECHING ]
[ SCREAMS ]
[ MUSIC STOPS ]
BILLY : Yeah , I 'm fine . Whatever .
MAN : You all right , man ?
- Hey , baby , come on , not now .
- Carter . CARTER : Oh .
It looks like we have a bit of a reunion here .
- Let it go . - When are you moving ?
A couple weeks .
- That 's too bad . BILLY : You dick .
- We 're losing our favorite teacher .
TERRY : Baby , come on .
Look , guys . There 's something I need to tell you , okay ?
- Alex . - And you lived here your whole life ? Yeah .
And now she 's gotta move all because of Browning .
Enough , both of you .
They died and we lived .
Get over it .
I will not let this plane crash be the most important thing in my life .
[ TERRY GRUNTS ]
I 'm moving on , Carter .
And if you wanna waste your life
beating the shit out of Alex every time you see him
then you can just drop fucking dead .
[ TIRES SCREECHING ]
WOMAN [ ON TV ] : Okay . MAN : You look like a smart shopper .
WOMAN : Well , thank you .
MAN : Let 's just say you were to see this knife set in a department store .
What do you think you 'd have to pay ?
[ PHONE RINGING ]
WOMAN : Wow , that 's a huge knife set , but how many- - ?
[ LINE RINGING ]
KEN : Hello ? - Is Alex there ?
Oh , hi , Clear . Yeah , just a minute .
It 's Clear again . You wanna talk to her ?
MAN [ ON TV ] : - -the economy kept trading volume below average today , and stocks- -
KEN [ OVER PHONE ] : Clear , he 's in the shower .
- Can I get him to call you back ? - Sure , bye .
She 's concerned about you .
I 'm concerned about you .
Why won 't you talk to her ?
Or me ?
- -which could put a cloud over both stocks and bonds .
Dad , you and Mom have both been a big help .
But there 's something I need to understand before I can talk to anyone .
- -the Dow down 75 .
The National Transportation Safety Board has a new theory tonight
on the possible cause of the explosion of Volée Air Flight 180 .
Officials believe deterioration of silicon insulation
on an electrical connector to the scavenger pump
may have leaked combustible fluids .
- A spark in the fuel switch ... - That 's Tod 's seat .
... in the fuselage may have ignited the fuel line and proceeded to the fuel pump
which would have set off the catastrophic explosion .
The path of the explosion .
Okay , the first was Tod .
Then it was Terry .
They 're dying in the order they would have died .
That 's death 's design .
Miss Lewton 's next .
LEWTON : And whenever I can fall asleep , I just ... .
I see Terry Chaney .
And in the day , out of nowhere
I hear the sound of my own voice in my head
saying to Larry Murnau :
" No , you know the whole French thing .
Get on the plane . "
Everything reminds me of that day .
Right , yeah .
I 'm hoping a change will help .
It 's just that I 've lived here my whole life , you know ?
And everywhere I looked were great memories .
And now all I see is Larry
and those kids , you know ?
Just looking out my own front yard makes me feel nothing but fear .
Laura , I 'm gonna have to call you back .
Right .
Hi , this is Valerie Lewton .
I need Agent Schreck .
What are you doing here ?
I was just ... .
I was checking the air in the tire to make sure it 's safe .
Get in the car .
Put on your seat belt .
I believe that Miss Lewton is next .
- Next ? - Yes .
Yeah , next , because there 's this pattern that 's occurring .
Oh , right , a pattern , yeah .
You noticed that too , huh ?
Mom 's favorite .
[ JOHN DENVER 'S " ROCKY MOUNTAIN HIGH " PLAYS ON STEREO ]
So , what about this pattern , Alex ?
Did you see it in another one of your visions ?
Did you catch it in some TV static ?
You know , I never asked for what happened on the plane .
You guys are gonna sit on your little chairs and make fun of me .
Whatever , it 's fine .
But I saved six lives on that plane .
Six lives , and everybody in my entire school thinks I 'm a freak .
And I 'm not- - I 'm not suffering from posttraumatic stress .
I don 't have a narcissistic deity complex .
I 'm not going Dahmer on you guys .
This just is .
There is a pattern for us all .
There 's a pattern for you , there is a pattern for you .
There 's a design for everyone .
I don 't know how yet .
But I 'm gonna break this one .
Alex , you came to our attention at first
because you were under suspicion in this plane explosion .
Now , I know you didn 't blow up the plane .
And we were ready to move on , but then the other survivors started to die .
First , your friend Tod .
Then Terry Chaney , while you were there at the scene .
And now tonight we pick you up at Val Lewton 's house .
Alex , nobody has control over life and death .
Unless they are taking lives and causing death .
Now , can you promise me that no one else is going to die ?
No , I can 't .
As long as I 'm in here , it 's out of my control , I 'm sorry .
Okay , go ahead .
Get out of here .
Thank you .
That kid gives me the creeps .
What are we gonna do ?
We got nothing to hold him .
That 's not what I 'm talking about .
There were a couple of moments there
where I almost believed him .
Can I tell you something ?
Don 't take this the wrong way .
But sometimes , you give me the creeps .
[ KETTLE WHISTLES ]
[ SCREAMS ]
You 've gotta stop this .
Stop this , it 's a stupid mug .
You 're out of here .
Pretty soon , you 'll be gone .
You 'll be gone .
[ GASPING ]
© P @ rM ! NdeR M @ nkÖÖ ™
©
© P @ rM ! NdeR
© P @ rM ! NdeR M @ nkÖÖ
Miss Lewton .
Okay , all right , okay .
Just stay still , okay ?
Oh , God . Oh , God . Miss Lewton .
Hey , Alex .
BILLY : Dude .
I don 't know where he is .
- He 's not talking to me . - Why ?
Because I didn 't believe him .
SCHRECK : If he does contact you
I think it would be in the best interest of your safety if you called us .
Now , here 's my card .
Toll-free number .
Interesting work .
[ HORN HONKS ]
BILLY : Carter , you dick .
[ BLADE SNAPS OPEN ]
CLEAR : What are you doing ?
Terry 's name should be on this wall .
Shit .
Why 'd you want us to meet you here anyway , huh ?
Because they 're watching me , see if I go to Alex .
That 's why you 're taking me .
Why would I wanna see him ?
Because he knows which one of us is next .
[ JANE SIBERRY 'S " ALL THE CANDLES IN THE WORLD " PLAYS ON CAR STEREO ]
So drive the speed limit , okay ?
Oh , and don 't pass on the right .
Billy , wait a minute here .
I 'm getting a vision .
You 're the next one , man .
Hey , man , why 'd you say that ?
Because if you say another word , I 'm gonna fucking kill you .
He could be anywhere from here to a mile down .
So you guys drive down there , we 'll meet around the middle .
It 'll take half the time .
Do you think they 're still up there ?
Somehow , Flight 180 , are they still in flight ?
Somewhere , are they safe ?
When I was a kid , like 6 or 7
I used to worry so much about my parents dying .
Lying awake at night just worrying .
Yeah , well , most kids do , I guess .
Most kids never have it happen .
When I was 10 , my dad went into a 7-Eleven for cigarettes .
I guess that he heard someone say , " Don 't turn around . "
So on reflex , or thinking it was a friend joking , he did .
And the guy blew his head off .
Life became shit after that .
My mom just couldn 't deal anymore .
She married this asshole
who my mom with my real dad would have crossed the street to avoid this guy .
He really didn 't want a kid .
So my mom didn 't either anymore .
If that was the design for my father and my family
then fuck death .
God , I have thought a lot about that somewhere , Alex .
It exists , that place .
Where my dad is still safe .
Where he had a full pack of cigarettes that night and just kept driving .
Where me and my mom and my dad are still together
and have no idea about this life here .
Where our friends are still in the sky .
Where everyone gets a second chance .
Alex , we can 't give up .
ALEX : Look , I can 't go home .
All right ? After Miss Lewton , they 're gonna be looking for me .
CLEAR : No , we 're taking you to my dad 's cabin .
It 's only a couple miles from my house .
All right , Browning , you fucking warlock .
Did you know about Miss Lewton , or what ?
Why do you think I was hiding ?
Billy told the FBI he saw you running from her house .
I was running because they blame me .
They blame me for Tod , they blame me for her , for the plane crash .
The fire , like , caramelized her blood , Alex .
Your shoe prints were in it .
Your fingerprints were on the knives .
I told you they were not- -
I 'm not talking about whether or not you did it .
Or even if you knew she was dead .
Did you know she was gonna be next before she was ?
Yeah , I did .
- I knew . - All right .
Out of us , who 's next to see it ?
Please , tell me I 'm gonna get to see the Jets win a Super Bowl .
It 's me , right ?
That 's why you 're not saying .
I knew I should have felt up Tammy in the pool that time .
What are you whining about ? I 'm next .
He didn 't say anything . Just drive .
You have a responsibility to tell me .
Do you think it 's gonna make it easier to know , Carter ?
Huh ? It 's not , it 's gonna make it fucking harder .
You know , you get off having control over me .
You let me decide how to deal with it .
It doesn 't matter who 's next .
Because we 're all on the same list . All of us .
Oh , fuck . Really ?
All right , then why bother ?
What 's the fucking point , right ?
Me and Terry , we 'll be back together on the other side , so why wait any longer ?
Carter , what are you doing ?
Carter , slow down .
- Slow down , Carter ! - Fuck you .
- Knock it off . - May as well go out on my own free will .
Not with us in the fucking car .
- Jesus , Carter , no . - Stop it .
Carter , stop the car .
Hey , what 's the worry if it ain 't your time ?
I could get nailed and you all wouldn 't give a shit , right ?
- It 's only me . - It doesn 't work that way , Carter .
And I fucking hated French class .
CLEAR : Control yourself . - That 's what I 'm doing .
I know what you 're doing .
And it 's all right to be scared .
I 'm not afraid , all right ?
I decide when it 's time .
I control my life , I control my death .
You don 't have to prove to us how big your balls are . Not now .
[ GRUNTS ]
Carter , stop driving like such an asshole .
What are you doing ?
Fuck it , Carter , Jesus Christ .
Carter , put your hands back on the wheel .
CLEAR : Carter , stop .
ALEX : Hands on the wheel , Carter .
Oh , shit .
ALEX : Okay , Carter , easy .
I am so close to puking right now , you don 't even wanna know .
CLEAR : We 're afraid too , Carter , but we 're not going to quit .
Stop what you 're doing and stop this fucking car .
Damn it , Carter .
I want you to stop this car right now .
[ ENGINE STOPS ]
[ TRAIN SIGNAL RINGING ]
[ WHISTLE BLOWING ]
- Billy . - Move it .
Hey , open the door , Billy .
Move the fucking car !
- Hey , open the fucking door .
CLEAR : Move the car .
ALEX : Open it .
CLEAR : Open the door . ALEX : Easy , easy , open the door .
CLEAR : Open the door .
ALEX : Billy , open the fucking door !
CLEAR : Billy , open it ! ALEX : Open the door !
CLEAR : Open the door !
Carter , listen to me .
Don 't do this .
CLEAR : Goddamn it !
Get out of the fucking car .
ALEX : Carter , listen to me .
Hey , listen to me .
This isn 't the way .
It 's not the way .
Get out of the car .
- Come on ! - It 's coming , it 's coming !
- Carter . - It ain 't my time .
[ ENGINE STRUGGLING ]
Oh , shit .
Carter , listen to me . This isn 't the way .
Get out of the car , Carter .
CLEAR : Carter , get out of the car .
ALEX : Come on , get out !
I can 't get out !
CLEAR : Alex ! No !
Man , he really is next .
- Get out ! - Get out !
- Come on ! - Fuck !
Oh , God .
I saw it . I saw the belt .
- Scared now ? - It broke .
Bullshit . He saved your life again .
That 's right .
You 're next , Carter .
I 'm staying the fuck away from you .
- Shut up . - We don 't need this shit right now .
I don 't need it ever . What are you doing ?
Get away from him , he 's next .
Hey , fuck you , Billy . I 'm not dead .
Oh , you will be .
You 're dead , you 're dead .
And you ain 't taking me with you !
CARTER : Oh , shit . Oh , shit .
Jesus fucking Christ !
You should 've been next .
You should 've been next after Lewton .
That 's the plan . That 's the design .
You should be dead .
You 're the fucking devil .
I saw the seat belt . I knew it would rip .
[ SIREN WAILING ]
That 's how I saved him . Just like the plane .
Just like the explosion , I saw it .
The police are coming .
Fuck , I saved him .
Because I saved him
it skipped Carter , went to the next in the path of the explosion , Billy .
I have to see it .
And if I see it , then I intervene .
And if I intervene , I cheat the design .
What , intervene ? What are you , God now ?
Gods aren 't afraid to die .
Gods don 't die . We do .
- You know ? - Baby , you 're losing it , okay ?
The police will be here .
We have to get you to my cabin .
You can hide , and get your head together .
Okay , after Billy , I 'm next . I 'm next .
- And then me . - Hey , hey , hey , listen .
I 'm not gonna let it happen , okay ?
- Listen to me , all right ? - Hey , hey , hey .
Why don 't you two just get the fuck out of here ?
Rusted .
Tetanus .
Nice one .
I overlooked it .
You tried to capitalize .
But I caught you , you fuck .
I can beat you .
Yeah , I mean , not forever , but I got this cabin rigged to beat you now !
She was there a minute ago .
What are you talking about ?
I 'm not turning him in .
It 's too dangerous for him out there alone .
- I go with you . - You can 't .
Clear , you just tell us where he is .
Wait at home , I give you my word
that we will bring him in safely in protective custody .
I never moved .
Christa asked me to change seats but I never moved .
I would 've been up next to Tod .
Fuck , why didn 't I remember that ?
I never moved . Clear 's seat was in front of mine .
She 's next .
[ SIRENS CHIRPING ]
Alex !
Come on , get in the car .
We 're going around . Get in the car .
Come on !
- Go ! MAN : Move !
[ DOG BARKING ]
Oh , shit .
SCHRECK : There ! WEINE : Come on , let 's go , over here .
SCHRECK : Alex !
Alex , we 're trying to help you .
Fritz , get away from it .
[ SCREAMS ]
Come on .
SCHRECK : Alex !
[ YELLS ]
Run !
[ GURGLING ]
We lost him .
From the direction , there 's only one place he 's heading .
No shit .
[ SCREAMS ]
[ GURGLING ]
[ GASPS ]
ALEX : Clear !
No .
Oh , my God .
Don 't move . Stay there .
Don 't move , don 't move .
Don 't touch anything .
You 're grounded by the tires , okay ?
The car 's gonna explode .
I can only hold on for so long , you know what to do .
Don 't !
When I do this , it 'll skip you , and it 'll be over .
- It 's the only way we can cheat death again . - No , don 't !
Clear , I am not gonna let it beat us both .
You know what to do .
I 'll always be with you .
No !
Alex ! Alex , get away from there .
Alex . Alex .
Damn it , you can 't do this to me .
Come on , baby . Come on .
WEINE : Alex , Alex ?
Alex , Alex ? Oh , shit , he 's not breathing .
Hold on , Alex . Come on , stay with me .
[ PEOPLE CHATTERING IN FRENCH ]
Well , we made it .
Paris , I can 't believe it .
I just can 't believe we got on a plane again .
You know what I 'm saying ?
[ WAITER AND ALEX SPEAK IN FRENCH ]
Wow .
It 's weird being here , huh ?
We finally completed a puzzle .
It 's just there 's something missing , you know ?
- To Terry . - Yeah .
- To Tod . - To all of our friends that can 't be here .
- Cheers . - Cheers .
What ?
If you would have told me six months ago
that the three of us would be sitting here having a drink ... .
- Yeah . CARTER : I don 't know .
I mean , sometimes it just feels like the two of you
are the only ones who can really understand .
You were right , Browning .
It did skip us . There was a design .
We beat it . You know , we won .
I think the only thing we won , Carter , is a chance at a full life .
A chance that I won 't ever waste .
Yeah , there 's just something ... .
You know , something I can 't figure out .
- What ? - About the design .
Alex , just let it go . All right ?
I swear- - Just hear me out , all right ?
- Oh , my God . - It 's just- - Listen .
Now , the path of the explosion determined the order of our deaths , right ?
When I intervened and saved Carter
it skipped him and went to the next person in the path . It went to Billy .
All right , and then it was Clear .
But I intervened and saved her , so it went to me , but in my case
no one intervened , right ?
I was thrown from that power line by the explosion .
- So-- - So why did it skip you , right ?
How do we know that this isn 't exactly what was meant to happen ?
That out of everyone on Flight 180 , you , me and Carter were meant to live .
Maybe that was the design all along .
- Or you could still be next . - Shut up , Carter .
What ? I didn 't make up the rules .
Somebody 's gotta intervene before death can skip them .
Alex proved that three times .
In the plane , with me , you .
For all I know , it could circle back and get us all again .
But I am the safest fucker in the world because you 're still next .
[ SINGING " ROCKY MOUNTAIN HIGH " ]
CLEAR : Can we just stop talking about this ?
Let 's figure out what we 're gonna do tomorrow .
© P @ rM ! NdeR M @ nkÖÖ ™
[ ALEX GASPING ]
I 'm gonna meet you back at the hotel .
Just wait , I 'll go with you .
No , just stay here .
Okay , Clear ? Just stay here .
All right ?
See , it 's true . I told you you were next , man .
Stop it , Carter .
CLEAR : Alex , wait .
- No , Clear , stay there .
Okay ? Stay away .
Alex !
[ MAN YELLS ]
I told you , you were next .
Then it just skipped me .
So who 's next ?
©
© P @ rM ! NdeR
© P @ rM ! NdeR M @ nkÖÖ